grabone.co.nz 2018-01-30

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy on the internet is important to us. As the internet offers the ability to collect certain types of information about users, we want you to understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of any information we gather. To that end, this privacy policy discloses what information we gather, how we use it, and how to request that we correct or change it.

### 1\. Collection of Information

back to top

 **1.1** We gather certain information about users of the GrabOne website (the Website). This information includes:

_(a)_ personal information, provided through voluntary registration as a Member or use of the Website (such as your first and last names and email address);   
_(b)_ personal information, provided to us by you for any purchase through the Website (such as credit card number, expiration date and authentication codes or related information);   
_(c)_ personal information, provided to us by you through any other method (including without limitation correspondence and discussions);  
_(d)_ information collected by us through click -tracking in relation to your use of the Website, including the content you upload and the content you access; and aggregated data, which tracks traffic to the Website; and cookies, which are pieces of information transferred to your computer hard drive for record keeping (such as your preferences on our Website). 

**1.2** Failure to provide necessary personal information when requested may result in certain functions of the Website not being available to you.

**1.3** You confirm that any personal information you provide is current, complete and accurate at the time you provide it, and you agree to maintain and update this information as required to keep it so.

### 2\. Use of Information

back to top

 **2.1** Any personal information you provide may be used for the following purposes:

_(a)_ to verify your identity and/or the accuracy of that information (including using the information to contact you);  
_(b)_ to send you correspondence to your nominated email address and mobile telephone number (including information about Deals, alerts about Offers and Deals on the Website, and other advertising content, marketing messages, promotional material and research content, including on behalf of third parties);  
_(c)_ to obtain feedback on a Deal you have participated in;  
_(d)_ to contact you as part of the transaction process when making an Offer or entering into a Deal;  
_(e)_ to monitor, develop and improve the Website and ensure that content of the Website is relevant to users and presented in the most effective manner for the user;  
_(f)_ to investigate any complaints relating to the misuse of the Website, a breach of the Terms or misconduct in relation to the Discussion Board;  
_(g)_ responding to any queries and/or comments you have sent to us;  
_(h)_ to evaluate your eligibility for certain types of goods, offers, products or services that may be of interest to you, analyse advertising effectiveness and for internal research purposes;  
_(i)_ to communicate and provide additional information that may be of interest to you about us, the Website, goods, offers, products, services, and other third parties, sometimes by combining your information with information from other sources;   
_(j)_ send you reminders, technical notices, updates, security alerts, support and administrative messages, service bulletins and requested information; and   
_(k)_ such other use that you authorise. 

**2.2** You will have the option to choose to not receive certain types of email communications from us, except for those that are absolutely necessary (including to provide you with details of any Offers you have made or Deals you have purchased). Emails will always contain a link at the bottom to be removed from our mailing list or you can unsubscribe via your Member account page.

**2.3** Credit card and billing information is obtained from you via a Secure Socket Layer connection (SSL), which is fully encrypted. This information and your other personal information will be kept safe and secure. We may use credit card or other payment account information provided by you to make withdrawals from your account in exchange for payment for any Goods or Services in a Deal and to provide you with advertising content, marketing messages, promotional material and other offers, including on behalf third parties. We do not share this information with any third party except for those companies responsible for processing credit card transactions for us. If you do not want us to store this information, please let us know at the time you enter these details (you will have the ability to do this on our payment page at the time you enter this information).

### 3\. Disclosure of Information

back to top

 **3.1** You agree that we may disclose your personal information (including, but not limited to, your name and contact details):

_(a)_ to provide Merchants and third party logistics providers with contact and delivery address details for the purpose of delivering Goods and Coupons to your chosen address and processing payment;   
_(b)_ to third parties for use to provide you with services related to your use of the Website, if it is required to fulfil those services;   
_(c)_ to Merchants and/or third parties where we have your consent, such as by opting-in to receive communications from Merchants and/or other third parties;   
_(d)_ to third party market research companies contracted by us to evaluate your eligibility for certain types of goods, offers, products or services that may be of interest to you, analyse advertising effectiveness and for internal research purposes;   
_(e)_ to enforce or apply the Terms of the Website;  
_(f)_ to the relevant authorities, any internet search provider that you use to access the Website, and/or the applicable intellectual property rights holders (or their representatives) if we consider you are infringing the intellectual property rights of any person; and   
_(g)_ where we consider in our absolute discretion we are required to disclose your personal information in accordance with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or Government request.  

### 4\. Cookies and Tracking

back to top

 **4.1** What Are Cookies?

These cookies are unfortunately not delicious little morsels of biscuity goodness, instead we use cookies to provide you with the best possible user experience. A cookie is a small, simple text file which is stored by your web browser (e.g. Google Chrome) on your computer or mobile device. Cookies allow us to tailor GrabOne to you as an individual and helps you to find the GrabOne deals that are most relevant to you. That makes the site faster and easier to use. And remember, cookies aren’t like James Bond. They don’t spy on you or sell your data on to the highest bidder. This Website uses cookies, and by continuing to use the Website we assume you agree to their use.

**4.2** What Do We Use Cookies For?

We may use a cookie file containing information that can identify the computer you are working from. This information will not identify you as an individual, as it only gives us details of your IP address, PC platform (e.g. Windows or Mac), web browser and domain (whether you are accessing the Website from within the country or elsewhere). We may use the information generated by cookies to:

_(a)_ track traffic patterns to and from the Website including information like the pages you visit, the time you spend on each page, the date and time of your visit, and referring pages (pages you came from or go to);  
_(b)_ ensure advertising is being shown to the most appropriate person and limit the frequency of display for certain ad formats;   
_(c)_ enable you to enter our Website and use certain services as a Member without having to log on each time and to visit Member-restricted areas of the Website; and   
_(d)_ use Google Remarketing in combination with Google Analytics to advertise online (third-party vendors, including Google, show our advertisements on sites across the Internet). Third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimise, and serve advertisements based on someone’s past visits to our Website. Users can opt out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customise Google Display Network advertisements using the Ads Preferences Manager. 

**4.3** Disabling Cookies

You can choose to refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser and/or deleting them from your hard drive. You do not need to have cookies turned on to browse the Website, however cookies must be enabled in order to login or make a purchase. If your cookies are turned off we will not have any control over the frequency of display of certain ad formats. This could affect your experience of the Website. Visit [http://www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) for a comprehensive guide on how to control and delete cookies on a wide range of web browsers and operating systems.

### 5\. Content providers, advertisers and partners

back to top

 **5.1** We do not control the practices of content providers, partners and advertisers connected with the Website and to whom you provide personal information whilst using the Website. Our Website contains links to other sites, which may not follow the same privacy policies as us. We recommend that you check any relevant privacy policies before providing your personal information to any third party.

### 6\. Analytics

back to top

GrabOne or our related companies contract with online measurement companies and other service providers to manage and optimise our Internet business and communications. These companies collect information about visits to our site to assist us in analysing the site's performance and advertising effectiveness and optimising the site for readers and marketers. Details of these service providers and the information they may collect can be found [here](http://new.grabone.co.nz/third-party-access-to-information).

### 7\. Security

back to top

 **7.1** While we take strict precautions to protect your personal information against unauthorised use or disclosure, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit or receive through the Website. These activities are conducted at your own risk.

### 8\. Changes to Policy

back to top

 **8.1** We reserve the right to change this policy at any time by notifying users of the existence of a revised policy by updating the "last updated" date at the bottom of this page. By continuing to use the Website, you agree to be abound by the amended policy. You should check from time to time to see if the policy has changed or not.

### 9\. Holding, Correcting and Updating

back to top

 **9.1** Any personal information that you provide to us will be collected and held by us at **NZME, 2 Graham Street, Auckland 1010, New Zealand**. Under the Privacy Act 1993 you have rights of access to and correction of personal information that we hold.

**9.2** Although we take reasonable steps to ensure that all data we use is accurate, we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary. We offer the ability for users to correct or change their personal information online at any time and as often as necessary.

**9.3** If you have any questions about how our services work or regarding this statement, [Contact Us](http://www.grabone.co.nz/contact-us).

* * *

_Updated: 17 November 2015_
